http://nsouk.co.uk/network-of-sikh-organisations-nso-privacy-policy/

Privacy policy
This privacy policy sets out how the Network of Sikh Organisations (NSO) uses and protects any information that you give to our charity when you use this website.
The NSO is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. This policy is effective from 23 May 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode
other information relevant to surveys
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
To distribute our quarterly magazine the Sikh Messenger to those who have subscribed
We may use the information to improve our communications and articles
We may periodically send emails updates, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for getting in touch, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@nsouk.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the Network of Sikh Organisations, 43 Dorset Road, Merton Park, London SW19 3EZ or alternatively e-mail us: info@nsouk.co.uk
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Follow us on
Recent Posts
Success in campaign against media’s use of the word ‘Asian’ to describe grooming gangs
A Gurpurab message
Marking the martyrdom of Guru Tegh Bahadur
The APPG for British Sikhs and hate crime: A flawed approach
Setting the record straight on anti-Sikh hate crime
Recent CommentsConcerns grow for British Sikh “illegally” arrested in India | SikhPA on The troubling case of Jagtar Singh JohalPositive outcome in NSOâ€™s campaign for separate recording of anti-Sikh hate crime | Network Of Sikh Organisations on Positive outcome in NSO’s campaign for separate recording of anti-Sikh hate crimeHow Governments Can Curb Anti-Sikh Discrimination | E-Radio.US on Positive outcome in NSO’s campaign for separate recording of anti-Sikh hate crimeSikh Peer Indarjit Singh calls for closure on Golden Temple attack | Network Of Sikh Organisations on Sikh Peer Indarjit Singh calls for closure on Golden Temple attackActivate and boycott | Naujawani.com on NSO urges all Sikhs to Boycott Downing Street Baisakhi ReceptionCategories
1984 (7)
1984 Sikh Genocide (21)
Current Issues (167)
Employment (3)
Human Rights (9)
Press Releases (130)
Publications (4)
Radio (5)
religious literacy (4)
Sikh Messenger (3)
Sikhism (10)
Thought for the day (42)
UKPW (2)
Uncategorized (19)
Videos (8)
Copyright © 2020 All rights reserved. Network of Sikh Organisations
Designed by
Pritpal S Makan
Skip to toolbar
About WordPressWordPress.orgDocumentationSupportFeedbackSearchLog In
<a href="http://www.makan.me.uk" title="www.makan.me.uk",'delicate'>
